

**Phone** 

317-910-5607

Email

drew@drewgoff.com

**Portfolio** 

https://drewgoff.com

**Address** 

1184 Bridgeport Drive Westfield, IN 46074

Education

## Indiana University

B.S. General Studies

Minors Psychology & Media Production

#### Recording Workshop

**Cert** Sound Engineering

## About

I currently work at Capital One as a UX/UI Developer. At Capital One, I work with designers and bring their designs to life by coding them in HTML, CSS (Sass) and Angular. My average day is spent coding, coming up with solutions to design problems and communicating with designers.

Previously I worked at Caterpillar inc, where I worked on a international team of designers and developers. They brought us all together to build the fourth generation operating system's user interface. We designed all of our work there in Illustrator and coded them as Web Components.

Before working at these two companies, I started my career a decade ago as a UX/UI Designer and worked my way into being a UX/UI Developer.

## Expertise

#### Technical Skills

#### Languages

- + HTML
- + CSS
- + SVG
- + JavaScript/ES6
- + JSON

#### Frameworks | Libraries

- + Angular
- + React
- + TypeScript
- + Sass
- + Stencil.js
- + Tailwind

#### Design

- + Sketch
- + Figma
- + InVision
- + Axure
- + Adobe Photoshop
- + Adobe Illustrator
- + Cinema 4D

## Experience

## **Capital One**

(Aug 2020 - Present)

**UX/UI** Developer (Contractor)

- + Work with designers and bring their designs to life in code. Code their designs in Angular, TypeScript, SVG, HTML and CSS (Sass).
- + Design interface components in Sketch and code them as components.
- + Part of a large development team that creates internal software applications for Capital One.

## **Caterpillar Inc.**

(Sep 2019 - May 2020)

**UX/UI** Developer (Contractor)

- + Brought on to design and build the 4th generation OS user interface for the Earth moving division. We designed the interfaces and coded them as web components (JavaScript, Shadow DOM, HTML, CSS, SVG) to support nine software teams around the world.
- + Created Axure Pattern libraries for our design system.
- + Wrote scripts, designed storyboards, did voiceover and created 2D/3D animations; in teaching the high level management about the cost benefits of creating a Design System for Caterpillar vehicles.



**Phone** 

317-910-5607

Email

drew@drewgoff.com

**Portfolio** 

https://drewgoff.com

Address

1184 Bridgeport Drive Westfield, IN 46074

## Community

### Deaconess Riley Children's Hospital

Worked on a team of designers, creating the designs for the new children's hospital. My primary role was as the photographer on the team. The large scale photography work is showcased throughout the hospital.

## References

# Tom Beccuee Manager at Caterpillar 309-202-7455

# Sarah Schonert Team Lead at Caterpillar 309-645-3619

# Ryan Stephens Technology Manager at Kroger Technology 270-832-5443

# Tara Blessinger Deaconess Designer 812-431-6199

# Laura Brown Marketing Manager 812-604-5649

Experience

## **UX Coding**

Product Designer

(Mar 2019 - Aug 2019)

- + Designed and Developed a web application that teaches UX Designers how to code through visual representations of how the code works.
- + Wrote and recorded my first classical piano album "Soulmate Sonata". Which has now been streamed by thousands of listeners in 11 different countries.

## **SIGMA Equipment**

(Sep 2016 - Feb 2019)

**UX/UI** Designer

+ Worked on a software team as the sole UX/UI Designer. Once design was completed, worked on the software team coding the designs into React.

## **OneMain Financial**

(Dec 2014 - Sep 2016)

**UX/UI** Designer

- + Designed the consumer facing mobile app which was available through the Apple IOS and Android store.
- + Designed 28 internal web applications with a team of 38 software engineers.
- + Developer and designer of the framework "OneMain Elements". What makes Elements unique is it's build using Object Oriented SASS (CSS) and JavaScript. What really makes it different though is that every object has been designed for exact measurements in Adobe Illustrator. This allows us to expedite UI development by reusing code and to create consistency among designs.

## **CNO Financial Group**

(Jun 2014 - Oct 2014)

Web Designer (Contractor)

## Truth@Work

(Jun 2012 - Jun 2014)

Director of Web and Multimedia Development

## INDYCAR Simona De Silvestro

(Jan 2012 - Jan 2014)

UX Designer, UI Developer and Photographer